=== Variation Monster ===
Contributors: wooxperto
Tags: Product Variation Table,Variation quick cart,Quick add to cart,variations table
Requires at least: 5.2
Tested up to: 6.7.1
Requires PHP: 7.2
Stable tag: 1.0.0
License: GPL v2 or later
License URI: https://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/gpl-2.0.html

Supercharge WooCommerce with a powerful variation management tool. Add an intuitive variations table and quick cart functionality directly on product pages for a seamless shopping experience.

== Description ==


WooCommerce Product Variation Table & Variation Quick Cart comes to make add to cart process faster for variable products. Most of the cases before adding a variation to cart there are some many clicks needed, which is time consuming. As a result most customers feel disappointed to choose the right variation. Ultimately business losses.

WooXperto is introducing a Product Variation table and quick cart plugin to solve this issue.


== Installation ==
1. Upload the Plugin Files: Upload the Product Variation With Quick Cart folder to the `/wp-content/plugins/` directory.
   2.Activate the Plugin: Activate the plugin through the \'Plugins\' menu in WordPress.
3. Install Required Plugins: Make sure WooCommerce is installed and activated.
4. Configure the Plugin: Go to \'Variation Table\' Settings\' under Admin Menu to configure the plugin

== Frequently Asked Questions ==
1. How Product Variation Table with Quick Cart work?
   It\'s display variations as a table of WooCommerce variable products.

2. Can i customize style of  Variable table?
   Yes, you can change variation table style easily.

== Screenshots ==
1. Product Variation Table Settings
2. Product Variation Table Style
3. Quick Cart Cart Popup

== Changelog ==
1.0.0